Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS.180
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Subject Files, 194392
  - Series II, Subseries A: Artists, 194442
    - Barnes and Noble, c.a. 1997; 194825 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Barry, Judith, 1985-1995; 194824 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Bartle, R.A., Bill Bell and Noa Hall, 1992; 194823 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Bartlett, Neil, Undated; 194822 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Barton, Nancy, 1991; 194821 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Baskerville+Watson, 1984; 194820 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      Postcard event announcement. Participants include Nan Goldin.
    - Bassara, Robert, 1997-2004; 194819 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Bee, Susan, 2000; 194818 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Bell, Hilary, c.a. 1996; 194817 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Bellamy, Dodie and Kevin Killian, 1995; 194816 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Bellmer, Hans, 2001; 194815 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Bergreen, Karen, 1998; 194814 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - The Bettys, 1980; 194813 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Blachly, Jimbo, 1998-1999; 194812 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Blagg, Max, 2002; 194811 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Blair, Dick and Jerry Phillips, 1998; 194810 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Bloom, Barbara, 1991-1999; 194809 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Blum, Andrea, c.a. 1997; 194808 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Bockris, Victor, [n.d.]; 194807 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - BOMB Magazine, 1998; 194806 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Bordowitz, Gregg, 1995-1996; 194805 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Bornstein, Jennifer, 1998; 194804 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Bourgeois, Louise, 1996-2003; 194803 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Breuer, Marco, 2002-2005; 194802 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Brown, Marie-Annick, 2000; 194801 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Brown, Wesley, 2001; 194800 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Buckley, Carmel, 1994; 194799 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Burckhardt, Rudy, 2000; 194798 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Burstein, Jessica, 1999; 194797 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Caire, Patrice, 1983; 194796 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Campo Baeza, Alberto, 2003; 194795 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Capa, Hubert (pseudonym), 1993; 194794 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Carey, Ellen, 1998-2002; 194793 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Carnegie Hall, 2001; 194792 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      Stagebill for Tibetan New Year's Celebration performance featuring David Bowie, Dana Bryant, Philip Glass, and more.
    - The Century Association, 1997; 194791 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - The Charles Cowles Gallery, 1996; 194790 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Charles, Denis, 1998; 194789 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Chase, Edward T., 1964-1997; 194788 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Clair, Stephen (Steve Ferguson), 1996; 194787 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Clark, Emilie, c.a. 2002; 194786 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Clark, Michael, 1992; 194785 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Clarke, Cheryl, 1988; 194784 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Clementine Gallery, 1998; 194783 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Cockcroft, Eva, Undated; 194782 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Cohen, Ze'eva, 2000; 194781 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Colo, Papo, 1997; 194780 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Colomina, Beatriz, 1996; 194779 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Cooper, Dennis, 1998; 194778 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Corner, Philip, 1980; 194777 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Cortez, Diego, 1976; 194776 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Cox, Renée, Undated; 194775 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Crary, Jonathan, 2000; 194774 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Curt Marcus Gallery, 1996; 194773 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Cyphers, Peggy, 1990; 194772 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Darboven, Hanne, 1996; 194771 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Davis, Lydia, 1996; 194770 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Davis, Taylor, 1997-1998; 194769 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Davis, Tim and John Godfrey, Undated; 194768 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - DeCarava, Ray, 1996; 194767 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - de Filippi, Fernando, 1979; 194766 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - de Saint Phalle, Niki, 2002; 194765 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Deutsch, David, 1996; 194764 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Diao, David, 1988; 194763 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Dickson, Jane, 1996-1997; 194762 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Dillon, Millicent, c.a. 2000; 194761 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Dion, Mark, 1998; 194760 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Debord, Guy, 1994; 194759 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - DNA Gallery, 1999; 194758 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - The Drawing Center, 2005; 194757 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Dreher, Peter, 1996-2002; 194756 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Drozdik, Orshi, 1990; 194755 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Dullsville, Undated; 194754 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Durant, Mark Alice, 1999; 194753 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Ebersole, Lucinda, 1997; 194752 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Einzig, Melanie, 1995; 194751 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Ellis, Stephen, 1986-1994; 194750 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Emigholz, Heinz, 1985-2000; 194749 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Engler, Brigitte, 1995; 194748 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Eno, Brian, 2000; 194747 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Epstein, Mitch, 2002; 194746 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Erhardt, Jean, 1992; 194745 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Ess, Barbara, 1979-2001; 194744 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Exit Art ***see also*** Oversize Series II, Subseries A, 2001; 194743 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Fagin, Steve, 199[8]; 194742 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Fairchild, B. H., 2002; 194741 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Fales Library, 1999-2001; 194740 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Falour, Lisa B., 2000; 194739 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Fence, 2002-2004; 194738 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Films de Femmes, 1997; 194737 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Findeisen, Raoul David, c.a. 1997; 194736 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Firestone, Shulamith, 1998; 194735 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1995; 194734 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Flynt, Robert, 2000; 194733 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1979-2003; 194732 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Ford, Charles Henri: Manuscript of "Life of a Child," part 1, Undated; 194731 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Ford, Charles Henri: Manuscript of "Life of a Child," part 2, Undated; 194730 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Fordham University, 1998; 194729 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Symposium on the legacy of Marshall McLuhan
    - Foster, Ken, 1998-2002; 194728 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - The Foundry Theatre, Undated; 194727 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Frailey, Stephen, Undated; 194726 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Francis, Linda, 1996; 194725 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Franklin Furnace, 2001; 194724 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Fraser, Andrea, Undated; 194723 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Fuller, Margaret / David Salle, Undated; 194722 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Gaddis, William, 1999; 194721 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Gallagher, Ellen, 2001-2002; 194720 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Gardner, Donald, Undated; 194719 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Garnet, Eldon, 1998; 194718 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Garrard, Rose, 1983; 194717 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Genzken, Isa, 2000; 194716 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Gerbault, Arthur, 1990-1992; 194715 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Gerson, Neville, Undated; 194714 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - "Get High Off the Midgets in El Salvador", Undated; 194713 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Gill, Brendan, 1998; 194712 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Ginka + Takako, 199[?]; 194711 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Ginsberg, Martha, 2001; 194710 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Giorno, John, 1978; 194709 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Glier, Mike, 1980; 194708 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Glück, Robert, 1998; 194707 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Gordimer, Nadine, 1983; 194706 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Görtler, Dirk / Chelsea Hotel Magazine, 1996; 194705 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Gourevitch, Philip, 1998; 194704 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Greenwald, Ted, c.a. 1980; 194703 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Grey Room, 2000; 194702 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Gross, Larry: Manuscript of "You Don't Know Where This Starts or Ends", Undated; 194701 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Guston, Philip, 1996; 194700 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Hailand, Tim, 1997; 194699 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Halley, Peter and Frank Kozik; Organized by Bob Nickas, 1997; 194698 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Hankowitz, Molly, 1993; 194697 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Harris, Lyle Ashton, 1997; 194696 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Harrison, Julie, 1987; 194695 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Hartley, Pat, Undated; 194694 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Hatje, Hannes, 1986-1991; 194693 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Hayman, Richard, Undated; 194692 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Hearn, Pat, 1995-2001; 194691 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      Two pieces moved to oversize folder
    - Heartfield, John, 1991-1993; 194690 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Hegge, James, 2001; 194689 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Heilmann, Mary, 2001; 194688 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Hein, Birgit, c.a. 1995; 194687 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Hell, Richard, c.a. 2001; 194686 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Hill, Rebecca, 1991; 194685 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Hiller, Susan, 1983-2001; 194684 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Hodges, Jim, 2002; 194683 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Hofstra, David: Agreements; correspondence; misc., c.a. 1990-1997; 194682 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; press clippings; press release; notes; lyrics (with Tillman); misc., c.a. 1975-1980; 194681 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; invoices, c.a. 1981; 194680 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      Handwritten performance notes/cheat sheets present on reverse side of some posters.
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; press clippings; photographs, c.a. 1980-1989; 194679 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Hofstra, David: Portraits by Andrew Hill and unknown photographer(s), c.a. 1990; 194678 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; press clippings; touring information; misc., 1990; 194677 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; press clippings; notes, 1990-1993; 194676 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance programmes; press clippings; press release, 1994; 194675 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers and programmes; press clippings; misc., 1995-1997; 194674 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers and programmes; press clippings; misc., 1998-1999; 194673 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Hofstra, David: Curriculum vitae / Discography, Undated; 194672 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Hofstra, Leonard, c.a. 1990-1991; 194671 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Holch, Meredith, 2000; 194670 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Holland, Robin, 1984; 194669 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Holzer, Jenny, 2002; 194668 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Home, Stewart: Articles and drafts of collaborations with Tillman; miscellaneous artwork, c.a. 2004; 194667 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Home, Stewart: Manuscript of "Cunt", Undated; 194666 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Home, Stewart: Manuscript of "69 Things to Do with a Dead Princess", Undated; 194665 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Home, Stewart: News clippings, 1997-1999; 194664 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Horn, Roni, 1996-1998; 194663 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Housing Works, c.a. 2005; 194662 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Howard, Richard, Undated; 194661 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Howland, Rebecca, 1996; 194660 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Hujar, Peter, 2000; 194659 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Hull, Steven, 1998-2002; 194658 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Hunter College, 1984-1997; 194657 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Indiana, Gary, c.a. 1981; 194656 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - International Center of Photography, 2001; 194655 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, Shelley, 2002; 194654 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Jaffe, Shirley, 1990; 194653 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Jarman, Derek, 1993; 194652 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Jellett, Mainie, 1991; 194651 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Jenkins, Janet, 1993; 194650 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Jerriese Johnson East Village Gospel Choir, 2001; 194649 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Johnston, Jill, 1998; 194648 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Jones, Bill T. and Arnie Zane, 1980; 194647 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Jones, Finola, 1994; 194646 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Jüdisches Museum der Stadt Wien, 1999; 194645 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Julien, Isaac, 2000; 194644 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Jusidman, Yishai, 2000; 194643 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Just Another Asshole, c.a. 1983; 194642 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Just, Marcel, 1977; 194641 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Kaplan, Daile, 1976; 194640 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Kaplan, Helene, 1976; 194639 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Kasper, M., 1985; 194638 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Katz, Leandro, 1977; 194637 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Keller, Marjorie, 1979; 194636 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Kelly, Mary, 1974-1990; 194635 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Kennedy, William, 2002; 194634 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Kettell Musial, Linda, Undated; 194633 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Khedoori, Toba, 1996; 194632 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Kiernan, Frances, 2000; 194631 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Kiesler, Lillian, 1979-2002; 194630 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Killing Joke, Undated; 194629 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - The Kitchen, 1986; 194628 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Knowlton, Win, 2002; 194627 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Kohlhofer, Christof, 1981; 194626 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Kolbowski, Silvia ***see also*** Oversize Series II, Subseries A, 1995-2004; 194625 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Kooning, Willem de, 1998; 194624 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Kramer, Margia, 1980; 194623 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1984-2001; 194622 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Kunstnernes Hus, 1997; 194621 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Kurgan, Laura and Renée Green, 1995; 194620 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Kwon, Suwon, 1997; 194619 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - LaBelle, Brandon, 1998; 194618 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Landers, Sean, 1990-1997; 194617 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Lastname, Bradley, c.a. 1979; 194616 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Lauterbach, Ann, 1979-2001; 194615 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Lawler, Louise, 1998-2004; 194614 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Lebowitz, Fran, 1997; 194613 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Lee, Mingwei, 2000; 194612 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Leibovitz, Annie, 2001; 194611 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Lerner, Lisa, 1997; 194610 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Letinsky, Laura, 2002; 194609 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Levi, Louise Landes, 1998; 194608 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Levin, David, 1993; 194607 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Levine, Sherrie, 1993-1996; 194606 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Levy, William and Willem de Ridder, Undated; 194605 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Lichtenstein, Miranda, 2001; 194604 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Liss, Carla, 1977; 194603 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Lleshanaku, Luljeta, 2002; 194602 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Longo, Robert, 2000; 194601 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - McCarthy, Paul, 1999-2001; 194600 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - McCollum, Allan, 1997; 194599 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - McCracken, John, 1997; 194598 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - McGrath, Patrick: Manuscript of "Blood and Water and Other Stories", Undated; 194597 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - McNulty, Faith, c.a. 1959-1990; 194596 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Malanga, Gerard, 1996-1998; 194595 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Malevich, Kazimir, 1991; 194594 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Malloy, Judy, c.a. 1981; 194593 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Manzini, Mario, Undated; 194592 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Marden, Brice, 2002; 194591 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Margolin, Deb, 1993-1998; 194590 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Marshall, Robert, 1998; 194589 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Martin, Katy and Amos Badertscher, 2001; 194588 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - The Mask: A Crime Drama by Bill Elverman, 194587 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Mathews, Harry and Alastair Brotchie, 1998; 194586 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Mathews, Harry and Lynn Crawford: Manuscript, Undated; 194585 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Matta-Clark, Gordon, 1999; 194584 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Maynard, Joe, c.a. 1997; 194583 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Medalla, David, 1996; 194582 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - The Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1997; 194581 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Mesches, Arnold, 1998; 194580 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - Messner, Ann, 1997; 194579 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - Miller, Kip, Undated; 194578 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Minter, Marilyn, Undated; 194577 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Moffatt, Tracey, 2000; 194576 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Molinaro, Ursule, Undated; 194575 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - Moriarty, Jerry, 1984; 194574 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Murray, Elizabeth, 1995; 194573 (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Murray, Tatyana, 2002; 194572 (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - The Museum of Modern Art, New York, 1980-1999; 194571 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Myles, Eileen, 1984-1992; 194570 (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Neary, Scott, 1980-1992; 194569 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Nepita, Rainer, 1998; 194568 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Nest: A Magazine of Interiors, 1998; 194567 (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - New Museum of Contemporary Art / Chelsea, 2004; 194566 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - The New School of Social Research, 1998; 194565 (Box 11, Folder 104)
    - Niedzviecki, Hal, c.a. 1997; 194564 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Norwest Corporation, Arts Program, 1990; 194563 (Box 11, Folder 106)
      Modernist Ceramics: 1880 - 1940
    - Nutting, Cherie, 2002; 194562 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - O.P Screen, Undated; 194561 (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - O'Brien, Glenn, 2000; 194560 (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - O'Gorman, Ned, Undated; 194559 (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - Ontological Hysteric Theater / Richard Foreman, Undated; 194558 (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - Oppenheim, Meret, c.a. 1990; 194557 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - The Orgone Cinema, 1997; 194556 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - Osterman, Georg, Undated; 194555 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - O'Sullivan, Denis, 1995; 194554 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - Palace: An Exhibition at Two Sites, 1997; 194553 (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - Pascucci, Ernest Charles, 1995; 194552 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Paul Kasmin Gallery, 1996; 194551 (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Penney, John, 1984; 194550 (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - Pepe, Sheila, 2002; 194549 (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Pfeiffer, Paul, 2001; 194548 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Philadelphia College of Art, 1982; 194547 (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - Piper, Adrian, 1991-2002; 194546 (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - The Poetry Project at St. Mark's Church, Undated; 194545 (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Pondick, Rona, 2004; 194544 (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Porter, Joe Ashby - Near Future Manuscript, 2005; 194543 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Postmasters Gallery, 1996; 194542 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Prina, Stephen; Mark Stahl and Christopher Williams (SENSITIVE), Undated; 194541 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Pushcart Press, 2004; 194540 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Quintana-Aguirre, Yadir A., 1998; 194539 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Rabinowitz, Jonathan, 2005; 194538 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Radul, Judy and Micheal Turner, 1998; 194537 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Rainer, Yvonne, 1971-2002; 194536 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Rankin, Aimee, 1985; 194535 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Rappaport, Mark, 1996; 194534 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Ratcliffe, Carter, 1997; 194533 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Rattray, David, c.a. 1983; 194532 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Rayns, Tony / Edinburgh International Film Festival, 1984; 194531 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Reedy, Carlyle, 1981; 194530 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Rexroth, Stevie, 2000; 194529 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Richard, Future Lounge, 1997; 194528 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Richter, Gerhard, c.a. 1998; 194527 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Robbe-Grillet, Alain and Catherine, Undated; 194526 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Robbins, Dave, Undated; 194525 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Robinson, Agnes, 1980; 194524 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Ross, Andrew, 1998-1999; 194523 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Rothuizen, Jan, 1999; 194522 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Royal Academy of Arts / The Pop Art Show, 1991; 194521 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Royal Albert Hall / "The Return of the Reforgotten: an evening of poetry and performance", 1995; 194520 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Ruthi, Andreas, 1997; 194519 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - St. Aubyn, Edward, 2003; 194518 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Santos, Rene, c.a. 1980; 194517 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Scheeman, Carolee, 1971-2002; 194516 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Scheeman, Carolee / "Imagining Her Erotics" manuscript, 2001; 194515 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Schneider, Gary, 1992-1996; 194514 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Schouten, Lydia, 1990; 194513 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Scott, James, 1994; 194512 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Shaw, Jim; Gary Simmons and Tony Oursler, 1997; 194511 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Shaw, Karen, 1976; 194510 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Sherman, Cindy, 1996-1998; 194509 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Simmons, Laurie, 1985-1998; 194508 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Simon, Adam, Undated; 194507 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Smegma the Magazine, 1980; 194506 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Jane Lawrence, 1985; 194505 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Smith, Kiki, 1992-2002; 194504 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Smith, Michael, c.a. 1983-1998; 194503 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Smith, Seton, 1993-1998; 194502 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Tony, 1998; 194501 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Smith, Valerie, 1988; 194500 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Snider, Stephanie, 2001; 194499 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Song, Suran, c.a. 2001; 194498 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Sontag, Susan, c.a. 1999; 194497 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Spiegelman, Art, 2000; 194496 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Splendora: A Musical, Undated; 194495 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Srivastava, Atima, 1991; 194494 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1997; 194493 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Steinke, Darcey, 1998; 194492 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Stockholder, Jessica, 1991-1997; 194491 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Sullivan, Billy, 2000; 194490 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Sutcliffe, James, Undated; 194489 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Sweeten, Natasha, 1996; 194488 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - The Swiss Institute, 2000; 194487 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Tabbi, Joseph, Undated; 194486 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Tansey, Mark, 1997; 194485 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Taubin, Amy, Undated; 194484 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Teare, Kevin, c.a. 2003; 194483 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Theater for the New City, 1985; 194482 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Thompson, Cheyney and Eileen Quinlan, 2001; 194481 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Thornton, Leslie: "The Great Invisible", c.a. 1993; 194480 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Tin Pan Alley, 1983; 194479 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Tisa, Ken, 1998; 194478 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Toibin, Colm, Undated; 194477 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Transparent Quartet, 1995; 194476 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Turtle Point Press / Brooklyn Museum of Art, Undated; 194475 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Tuten, Frederic, 1997; 194474 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Tyler, Laura G. (Gail), 1997; 194473 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Ultra Vulva, Undated; 194472 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Union Gaucha Productions, 2001; 194471 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Valderrey, Edo, 1996; 194470 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - van Dalen, Anton, Undated; 194469 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Venice Biennale, 2001; 194468 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Vermeer, Johannes, 1996; 194467 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Vitra Design Museum, Undated; 194466 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Vorres Modern Art and Folk Museum, Undated; 194465 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Walker, Kara, 1998; 194464 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Watney, Simon, 1992-1993; 194463 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Wedge Press, 1983; 194462 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Welling, James, 1997-1998; 194461 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Wethli, Mark, 1995; 194460 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Weissman, Benjamin, 1982; 194459 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Wexner Center for the Arts / Debra Bricker Balken and Bill Horrigan, 1994; 194458 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Whetstone, Jeff, 2002; 194457 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1999-2003; 194456 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Wiese, Allison, 2004; 194455 (Box 12, Folder 88)